Guide to the George Nicolau Papers WAG.250
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Verizon / CWA (Quotas), 362552 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Verizon PA / CWA (13-04-56V; 0041-04; assignment administrators), 362551 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Verizon PA / CWA (022-04), 362550 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Verizon PA/ CWA (Flood), 362549 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Verizon PA / CWA (Torres), 362548 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Verizon / CWA (Cadillac Arbitrations), 362547 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Bell Telephone Company of PA / Federation Telephone Workers of PA, 362546 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- New York Telephone Company / Union of Telephone Workers (Rosado), 362545 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Bell Atlantic VA / CWA (Roper), 362544 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Verizon / IBEW, Local 2213 (Baker), 362543 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- United Telephone Company of New Jersey / CWA (Wilson), 362542 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- CSX Lines, Inc / District No. 1 MEBA (Baxter), 362541 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Central Gulf Lines (M/V Nordic Louisiana), 362540 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- District No. 1 MEBA / MORMAC Marine Enterprises (Maritrans Dispute), 362539 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Farrell Lines, 362538 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Lyons), 362537 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Tanker Service Committee (Tug Barges), 362536 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Derke), 362535 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Matson Navigation Company (Gamba), 362534 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Matson Navigation Company (Hubner), 362533 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- District No. 1 MEBA / MORMAC Marine Enterprises (Porta-Potty Grievance), 362532 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- District No. 1 MEBA / MORMAC Marine Enterprises (Samolchuk), 362531 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- District No. 1 MEBA / MORMAC Marine Transport (Wojcik), 362530 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Solomon), 362529 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Gallagher), 362528 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- NMU Plans / Costal Barge Corporation, 362527 (Box 13, Folder 40)
- District No. 1 MEBA; NMU / Tanker Service Corporation (Sperounces), 362526 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- District No. 1 MEBA; NMU / Tanker Service Committee and Marine Service Committee (Marine Index Bureau Reports), 362525 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- District 4 NMU/MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Marine Reliance), 362524 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- District 4 NMU/MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Fields), 362523 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- District 4 NMU/MEBA / Marine Transport Lines (Oilers), 362522 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Sea-Land Service (Wage Deferral Dispute), 362521 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Sea-Land Service (Christmas Bonus), 362520 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- District No. 1 MEBA / Sea-Land Service (Smith), 362519 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / CWA (C. Awkward), 362518 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Bell Atlantic - NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00453 93S; Watkins), 362517 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0009 91S; Ackerman), 362516 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (00371 91S; Sten), 362515 (Box 13, Folder 52)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0096 88S; Pirecki), 362514 (Box 13, Folder 53)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0153 90S; Boyd), 362513 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- Bell Atlantic- NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00670 92S; Marks), 362512 (Box 13, Folder 55)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0345 88S; Zabreski), 362511 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0188 90S; Hernandez), 362510 (Box 13, Folder 57)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0241 88S; Non-Employee Escorts), 362509 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (02794; Torres), 362508 (Box 13, Folder 59)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0297 97S; Compano), 362507 (Box 13, Folder 60)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (00305 91S; Travaille), 362506 (Box 13, Folder 61)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0323 90S; Hanley), 362505 (Box 13, Folder 62)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0336 89S; Reilly), 362504 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW (0402 87S; Nolan), 362503 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (00415 90S; Muschko), 362502 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0443 90S; Smreczak), 362501 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0659-86; Fox), 362500 (Box 13, Folder 67)
- Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (119 99; E. Post), 362499 (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00142 01; J. Martorano), 362498 (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (15046 02), 362497 (Box 13, Folder 70)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (1882 85; Johnson), 362496 (Box 13, Folder 71)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (2006 85S; HCP Records Clerks Doing CLA Work), 362495 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- Bell Atlantic NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00227 97), 362494 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Verizon Connected Solutions / IBEW, Local 827 (00361 00; Chase), 362493 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Bell Atlantic NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00396 93S; Maccar), 362492 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00398 99; Hess), 362491 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Bell Atlantic-NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (00419 93S; Darrah), 362490 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Bell Atlantic-NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (0519 90; Retirement Planning Seminar), 362489 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Verizon, NJ / IBEW, Local 827 (8484 1; Thatcher), 362488 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (0627 86S; Sullivan), 362487 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone / IBEW, Local 827 (1318-71) (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Verizon NJ / IBEW Local 827 (21837 03; Palma), 362486 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Actors Equity / Phoenix Theatre (General), 362485 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Actors Equity / Godspell Company and Edgar Lansbury, Joseph Beruh, and Stuart Duncan, as Producers of Godspell, 362484 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Actors Equity / Naura Hayden (Be Kind to People Week), 362483 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- AEA / Wulp and Berlind, Producers of Lydie Breeze, 362482 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- AEA / Coachlight Dinner Theatre, 362481 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- AEA / Theater West, 362480 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- CUNY / Adelman, 362479 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Margaret Alston), 362478 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Annual Leave), 362477 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Ashforth, et al., Brooklyn College), 362476 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Rosalind Barnes), 362475 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Board of Higher Education of New York City / Lloyd B. Barzey (Individual Grievant), 362474 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Georgia Baumbach), 362473 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Steven Berenback Hunter College), 362472 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Best, Lehman College), 362471 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Professor Irwin Blatt), 362470 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Buchen), 362469 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Buxbaum), 362468 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Cadieu Queens College), 362467 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Change of Working Conditions), 362466 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Board of Higher Education of the City of New York / Robert Daniel, 362465 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (J. Marion Dickey Queens), 362464 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Downer-Brooklyn College), 362463 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Drucker), 362462 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Fallon), 362461 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Dr. James Fetzer), 362460 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Floeter), 362459 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Jehousa Friedman / Trustees of the City University of New York, 362458 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Gamble), 362457 (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Gibbs, Montague, and Sellars), 362456 (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Grant), 362455 (Box 14, Folder 40)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Greenwald and Swiderski), 362454 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Ralph Green / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York, 362453 (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Hank), 362452 (Box 14, Folder 43)
- City University of New York / Professional Staff Congress (CUNY) Harris and Jacobs), 362451 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Norman P. Horwitz / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York, 362450 (Box 14, Folder 45)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Jansons), 362449 (Box 14, Folder 46)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Janus), 362448 (Box 14, Folder 47)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Jones/ Medgar Evers College), 362447 (Box 14, Folder 48)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Joseph), 362446 (Box 14, Folder 49)
- Arlene Mantell Kahn / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York, 362445 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Leake), 362444 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Anthony LoSecco / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York, 362443 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Leonard), 362442 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Lovell), 362441 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Leifer), 362440 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Macri), 362439 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Macri, II), 362438 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Samuel Margulies / Board of Higher Education, 362437 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Martindale), 362436 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Nicholas Mauro / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York, 362435 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Mayhew), 362434 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / CUNY (Normore), 362433 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Ndeli and Thaxton), 362432 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Moss), 362431 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Monroe), 362430 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Mendes), 362429 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Mehta), 362428 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Kevin McNulty / Board of Higher Education, 362427 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Seidman), 362426 (Box 14, Folder 69)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Ross), 362425 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (A. Rosenthal), 362424 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Charles Romain), 362423 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Richmond), 362422 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- Lewis A. Ress / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York, 362421 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Reiff), 362420 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Ramjerdi), 362419 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- Seymour W. Pustiknik / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York, 362418 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Posementier), 362417 (Box 14, Folder 78)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Pasamanick), 362416 (Box 14, Folder 79)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Wimberly), 362415 (Box 14, Folder 80)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Vlahovic), 362414 (Box 14, Folder 81)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Tottossy), 362413 (Box 14, Folder 82)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Toomey), 362412 (Box 14, Folder 83)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Tomlinson), 362411 (Box 14, Folder 84)
- Zoltan Tar / Trustees of the City University of New York, 362410 (Box 14, Folder 85)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (E. Smith), 362409 (Box 14, Folder 86)
- Carole Sirovich / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York, 362408 (Box 14, Folder 87)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Simonetti), 362407 (Box 14, Folder 88)
- Nathan Waldman / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York, 362406 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Ruth Westheimer / Trustees of the City University of New York, 362405 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Winer), 362404 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Edward Wolfarth / Board of Higher Education of the City of New York, 362403 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Trustees of the City University of New York (Vollmer), 362402 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Voorsanger), 362401 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Professional Staff Congress- CUNY / Board of Higher Education (Wydro), 362400 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- MLB 91-4 (Carlos Diaz), 362399 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- MLB 91-1 (Nieves), 362398 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- MLBPA (Garvey), 362397 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- MLB 91-6, 7, & 8 (Stottlemyre, Pittman, & Curry), 362396 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- MLB 93-1 (Designated Player), 362395 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- NN 84-80N (NABET/NBC), 362394 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- NN 84-100 (NABET/NBC), 362393 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- NN 84-163 (NABET/NBC), 362392 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- NN 84-164 (NABET/NBC), 362391 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- NN 84-201 (NABET/NBC), 362390 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- NN 84-202 (Harris), 362389 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- NN 85-1 (NABET/NBC), 362388 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- NN 85-8 & 12 (NABET/NBC), 362387 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- NN 85-25 (NABET/NBC), 362386 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- NN 85-74 (NABET/NBC), 362385 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- NN 85-83 (NABET/NBC) (Lee), 362384 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- NN 85-130 (NABET/NBC), 362383 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- NN 86-45 (NABET/NBC), 362382 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- NN 86-202; 20.10 (NABET/NBC), 362381 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- NN 87-1 (NABET/NBC), 362380 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- 2013 Donation – Arbitration Awards: Broadcasting, Health Care (Local 1199), Maritime, Communication, Theater, and Transportation, 1981-2013; 2013.043; 487835 (Box 23)
- 2013 Donation – Arbitration Awards: Airlines, 2002-2013; 487836 (Box 24)
- 2013 Donation – Arbitration Awards: National Basketball Players Association and Ad Hoc, 1990-2012; 487837 (Box 25)